Guide to the Yale Repertory Theatre Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the managing director and associate managing director, 1982-2003; Accession 2007-A-098
  - REP 3 CRUMBS FROM THE TABLE OF JOY
    - Rehearsal notes, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Script, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Licensing agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - REP 4 MEASURE FOR MEASURE
    - Guest artist, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Calendar and contact sheet, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Casting, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - House management, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Performance reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Production notes, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Program and promo material, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Rehearsal reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Script, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - REP 5 GLASS MENAGERIE
    - NY rehearsal space, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Performance reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Production notes, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Calendar and contact sheet, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Casting, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Licensing, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - House manager, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Housing, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Endgame, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Director, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Program and promo, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Rehearsal reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Guest artists, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Script, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - REP 6 HAY FEVER
    - Calendar and contact sheet, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Casting, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Director, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Housing, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Licensing agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Performance reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Production, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Program and promo, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Rehearsal reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - House management reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Script, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Performance reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Program, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Contact sheets, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Press releases, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
    - Guest artists, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - YSD 1 GREAT MEN OF SCIENCE
  - Great Men of Science, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Calendar, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Licensing agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Production notes, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Script, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Life is a Dream script and Misc., 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - YSD 2 TWELFTH NIGHT (Box 6)
  - Contacts and calendar, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Production, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Rehearsal reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Script, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - YSD 3 THE GOLEM (Box 6)
  - Calendar and contract, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Licensing agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Rehearsal reports, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Production, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - ACTORS (Box 6)
  - Soccorro Santiago, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
  - Dean Nolan, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
  - BREATH BOOM
    - Auditions, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Payroll, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - China Lee, costume designer, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - FIGHTING WORDS
    - Production meetings minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Licensing agreement, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - CHANGES OF THE HEART
    - Magico Pat Diamond, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - School Shows: General info, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - CORIOLANUS
  - PSYCHIC LIFE OF SAVAGES
    - Licensing agreement, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Corrine Larsen, costume designer, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Payroll, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Program, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - TCG Fiscal Survey 2000, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - Warner Brothers Studio licensing, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - Glick and Weintraub correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - YRT/YSD 2000-2001 season planning, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - Budget Statistics, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - Press coverage, 2002-2003 (Box 8)
  - AEA Bond
    - 1990-2001 (Box 8)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 9)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 9)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 9)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 9)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 9)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 9)
  - Third Year Acting Class AEA (Box 9)
  - AEA Bond 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - AEA Bond 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - AEA Bond 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - AEA Bond 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - Budget
    - 1997-1998 (Box 9)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 9)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 9)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 9)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 9)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Casting Directors 1997-1998 (Box 9)
  - 1997-1998 Casting (Box 9)
  - Casting 1996-1997 (Box 9)
  - Casting 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Casting Surveys (Box 9)
  - Casting 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Housing 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Housing 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - SSDC (Box 9)
  - SSDC, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - SSDC, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Costanza Romero costumes Troilus (Box 9)
  - AEA Directors, Designers, Musicians and Stage Managers
    - Musicians, Miscellaneous musicians, 1985-1999 (Box 10)
    - Musicians, Andrews, Dwight (Box 10)
    - Musicians, Bloom, Jane Ira (Box 10)
    - Musicians, Philippe, Bodin (Box 10)
  - STAGE MANAGERS
    - Surah Gormley Plass, 1985-1999 (Box 10)
  - YSD #4, Life is a Dream licensing agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Production, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Grapes of Wrath, miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - The Golem, script (3), 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Case Studies Guthrie Theater, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Cast Studies Guthrie Theater, 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - TAMING OF THE SHREW
    - Show press, 2002-2003 (Box 11)
    - Kronos music rights, 2002-2003 (Box 11)
  - THE BLACK MONK
    - Press (Box 11)
    - Contact Sjeets (Box 11)
    - Production meetings, budget info (Box 11)
    - Licensing agreement (Box 11)
    - Horse (Box 11)
    - Music Rights (Box 11)
    - musicians (Box 11)
    - NY Rehearsal Rentals (Box 11)
  - Johnson-Liff Casting (Box 11)
  - Johnson-Liff Casting (Box 11)
  - SSDC Season Forms (Box 11)
  - Program and box office reports (Box 11)
  - THE AMERICA PLAY
    - Co-production agreement (Box 11)
    - ICM Contract, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
    - Sound Designer (Box 11)
  - YSD- Love of three Oranges, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - YSD -Peer Gynt (Box 11)
  - YSD -the Cherry Orchard (Box 11)
  - BETTYS SUMMER VACATION -Matthew Cowles, 2001-2002 (Box 11)
  - Ben Mordecai, educational materials, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Commercial Theatre/Course Syllabi (Box 12)
  - MIF (Box 12)
  - Advanced Marketing Research (Box 12)
  - Management Seminar (Box 12)
  - FEDPT reading (Box 12)
  - American Theatre Practice, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Harvard Business Review (Box 12)
  - Sample Agreements (Box 12)
  - Johnson and Johnson Company Video (Box 12)
  - LORT File #1 AEA, 1995-1996 (Box 13)
  - LORT File #2 AEA, 1999-2005 (Box 13)
  - LORT File #3 SSDC, 1996-2001 (Box 13)
  - LORT File #4 SSDC, 1993-1996 (Box 13)
  - LORT File #5 USA, 1999 (Box 13)
  - LORT File #6, 1999 (Box 14)
  - LORT File #7 Dramatists Guild, 1998 (Box 14)
  - LORT File #8, 1998 (Box 14)
  - LORT File #9 LORT conference and minutes, 1984-1999 (Box 14)
  - LORT File #10 LORT mailing lists, 1998 (Box 14)
  - The Adventures of Amy Boch (Box 15)
  - Antigone innew York (Box 15)
  - As You Like It (Box 15)
  - Betrayal (Box 15)
  - Big Night (Box 15)
  - The Birds (Box 15)
  - Candida (Box 15)
  - Cure at Troy (Box 15)
  - Cure of the Starving Class (Box 15)
  - The Cryptogram (Box 15)
  - Dario Fo (Box 15)
  - First Lady (Box 15)
  - Galileo (Box 15)
  - The Glass Menagerie (Box 15)
  - The Green Bird (Box 15)
  - Hay Fever (Box 15)
  - It Pays to Advertise (Box 15)
  - Landscape of the Body (Box 15)
  - Midsummer (Box 15)
  - Oleanna (Box 15)
  - Pope and Witch (Box 15)
  - Richard III (Box 15)
  - Royal Shakespeare Company (Box 15)
  - School for Wives (Box 15)
  - Serious Money (Box 15)
  - Shrew (Box 15)
  - Skin of our Teeth (Box 15)
  - Theatre de Complicite (Box 15)
  - You Never Can Tell (Box 15)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession (Box 15)
  - DB Woodside, Count Bellair, The Beaux Strategem, 1995-1996 (Box 15)
  - Oleanna, royalties, contract, etc., 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - A Place with the Pigs (Box 15)
  - Actors Equity, 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - AEA Categorization (Box 15)
  - AEA Employment and casting Practices Survey, 1986-1989 (Box 15)
  - Actors Equity, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - AEA misc., 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Actors Equity, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Actors Equity, 1989-1990 (Box 15)
  - LORT Correspondence: General (Box 15)
  - AEA Bond, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - 1984 Security Agreement (Box 15)
  - 1992-1993 Security Agreement (Box 15)
  - Cast Studies (Box 15)
  - Moscow Art Theatre, 1994 (Box 16)
  - The Wooster Group, 1992 (Box 16)
  - Tri-Theatre Case Study, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Guthrie Theatre, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Big Night, 1990 (Box 17)
  - THE BIRDS Rep 5,Len Jenkin, adaptor, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
  - The Way of the WorldRep 4, Beineke Group Sales (Box 17)
  - CCA Grant (Box 17)
  - YSD/YRT Completed Applications (Box 17)
  - YRTCCA '01 Grant, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
  - Casting information (Box 17)
  - Misc. show info (Box 17)
  - Performance reports (Box 17)
  - House manager reports (Box 17)
  - Rehearsal reports, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
  - Daily Schedules (Box 17)
  - Production notes (Box 17)
  - Misc w/h applications, 1986-1988 (Box 18)
  - Foreign Festivals (Box 18)
  - Receipts A Walk in the Woods (Box 18)
  - Program, A Walk in the Woods (Box 18)
  - Job Applications/business manager (Box 18)
  - Job applications/marketing director (Box 18)
  - Job descriptions, 1996 (Box 18)
  - General Manager resumes (Box 18)
  - General manager position, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Press Resumes (Box 18)
  - NEA on-site evaluation (Box 18)
  - NLRB (Box 18)
  - Non-traditional casting policy (Box 18)
  - O'Neill Committee: Long Day's journey into night (Box 18)
  - O'Neill Centennial (Box 18)
  - Park Plaza Contract (Box 18)
  - Production history: YRT (Box 18)
  - Simon and Kumin (Box 18)
  - Survey information (Box 18)
  - Theatre magazine misc (Box 18)
  - Victor Adding machine (Box 18)
  - Buzz Ward (Box 18)
  - Who's Who (Box 18)
  - 1styr. rotations (Box 18)
  - YRT/YSD Brief history (Box 18)
  - Telemarketing Group Sales Plan 92, 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Marketing 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Marketing 1991-1992, single tickets (Box 19)
  - AAAE-meeting schedules (Box 19)
  - AAAE (Box 19)
  - SSDC 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - LORT SSDC Work stoppage Notice (Box 19)
  - ATPAM (Box 19)
  - International Programs (Box 19)
  - Association for Theatre in Higher Education (Box 19)
  - Commercial Theatre Institute (Box 19)
  - National Theater Conference (Box 19)
  - TCG (Box 19)
  - TCG Atlanta, January 14-16, 1994 (Box 19)
  - League of American Theatres and Producers (Box 19)
  - ACUCAA (Box 19)
  - Alliance of Arts Advocates (Box 19)
  - American Arts Alliance (Box 19)
  - ART Membership (Box 19)
  - Arts Council of New Haven (Box 19)
  - British American Drama Academy (Box 19)
  - Commercial Theatre Institute (Box 19)
  - Connecticut Advocate for the Arts (Box 19)
  - Connecticut Arts Endowment (Box 19)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 19)
  - FEDAPT
  - First New York International Festival of the Arts (Box 19)
  - International Theatre Institute (Box 19)
  - League of American Theatre 1991 Industry Conference Planning Committee (Box 19)
  - League Conference Toronto Oct. 25-27, 1991 (Box 19)
  - League of Connecticut Theatres (Box 19)
  - Management Consultants for the Arts (Box 19)
  - Museum of American Theatre (Box 19)
  - National Arts Stabilization Fund (Box 19)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 19)
  - National Theatre Conference (Box 19)
  - Performance Studio (Box 19)
  - Philadelphia Festival for New Plays (Box 19)
  - Pulitzer Luncheon (Box 19)
  - Stage Directors and Choreographers Foundation (Box 19)
  - Wisdom Bridge (Box 19)
  - Shubert Organization (Box 19)
  - TDF (Box 19)
  - United Scenic Artists (Box 19)
  - Head shots, 2002-2003 (Box 20)
  - Ben Mordecai Files I, 1982-1989 (Box 20–21)
  - HEAVEN
  - Licensing agreement, 2000-2001 (Box 22)
  - House management report (Box 22)
  - Injury Report Forms (Box 22)
  - Rehearsal/Performance Schedule (Box 22)
  - Production Meeting Notes (Box 22)
  - Casting (Box 22)
  - Rehearsal/Performance Reports (Box 22)
  - Future Productions (Box 22)
  - Royalty Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 22)
  - RICE BOY
  - Financials (Box 22)
  - Rachana v. Singh, SM (Box 22)
  - Casting (Box 22)
  - Script (Box 22)
  - Singapore Tour budgets (Box 22)
  - Licensing agreement, 2000-2001 (Box 22)
  - HEAVEN
  - O'Keefe Masters Tea "Raising" (Box 22)
  - RICE BOY
    - Production mtg. reports (Box 22)
    - Accident/Injury reports (Box 22)
    - Rehearsal notes and schedules (Box 22)
    - Performance reports, 2000-2001 (Box 22)
  - MUMP AND SMOOT, 2000-2001
    - Financials (Box 22)
    - VISA info (Box 22)
    - Travel (Box 22)
    - Performance Reports and Schedules (Box 22)
    - Presenting contract (Box 22)
    - Royalty reports (Box 22)
  - YSD 1 The Striker (Box 22)
  - YSD 2 Caucasian Chalk circle (Box 22)
  - YSD 3 Master and Margarita (Box 22)
  - Lower Depth -first year project (Box 22)
  - CWP/Playwriting contracts (Box 22)
- Records of playwright August Wilson, 1985-1996; Accession 2008-A-061
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032.
  Scope and Contents
  Pulitzer-prize winner August Wilson wrote 10 plays, each set in a different decade, chronicling the African-American experience during the 20th century. Six of these debuted at the Yale Repertory Theatre: "Ma Rainey's Black Bottom" (1984), "Fences" (1985), "Joe Turner's Come and Gone" (1986), "The Piano Lesson" (1987), "Two Trains Running" (1990) and "Radio Golf" (2005). The other plays in the cycle are "Jitney," "Seven Guitars," "King Hedley" and "Gem of the Ocean." Seven of the plays, including the first five that debuted at the Yale Rep, went on to Broadway.
  - "Ma Rainey's Black Bottom," production and prompt book (Maggie Adair), demo tape not received, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Two Trains Running," marketing, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - O'Neill Theater conference playbills featuring August Wilson, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Fences," profit distribution, 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5-10)
  - "Piano Lesson," box office numbers, 1990-1991, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Seven Guitars," weekly sales report, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "Joe Turner's Come and Gone," assignment agreement, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Audiovisual materials
    - Two Trains Running" demo tape, commercially produced audiocassette, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Piano Lesson, three commercially produced audiocassettes, 1990 (Box 5–7)
- Yale Repertory Theatre posters, 1966-1999; Accession 2008-A-108
  - 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - A Doll House, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - A Lesson from Aloes, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - A Moon for the Misbegotten, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - A Place with the Pigs, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - A Play of Giants, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - A Raisin in the Sun, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - A Touch of the Poet, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - A Walk in the Woods, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - About Face, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Ah! Wilderness, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Almost by Chance a Woman: Elizabeth, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - As You Like It, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Bacchae, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Bingo, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Boesman and Lena, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - Bosoms and Neglect, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Buried Child, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Cobb, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Crimes and Crimes, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Curse of the Starving Class, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Don Juan, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Dynamite Tonite, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Galileo, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - General Gorgeous, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - God Bless, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Greatshot, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Happy End, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - Hayfever, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Heartbreak House, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Hedda Gabler, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - Hello and Goodbye, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Henry IV, Part I, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Intermezzo, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Ivanov, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Johnny Bull, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Julius Caesar, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Kiss of the Spiderwoman, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Largo Desolato, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Life is a Dream, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - Little Eyolf, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Macbeth, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Mahagonny, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Major Barbara, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Man is Man, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Marriage, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Measure for Measure, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Melons, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Metamorphoses, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Miss Julie, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Mistaken Identities, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Mister Puntila and his Chauffeur Matti, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Moon Over Miami, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Neapolitan Ghosts, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Night is Mother to the Day, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - On the Verge, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Othello, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Peter and Wendy, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988-1999 (Box 2)
  - Pygmalion, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Reunion, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Richard II, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Rip Van Winkle, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Sarcophagus, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Saved/2 Yale Plays, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Scapin, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Search and Destroy, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Sganarelle, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Shaft of Love, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Story Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Suicide in B Flat, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Summer and Smoke, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - Talley's Folly, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Tartuffe, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Terra Nova, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - The Alchemist, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - The Blood Knot, 1986-1986 (Box 2)
  - The Bundle, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - The Durango Flash, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - The Father, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - The Glass Menagerie, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - The Government Inspector, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - The Idiots Karamazov, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - The Little Mahagonny and The Seven Deadly Sins, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - The Magnificent Cuckold, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - The Miser, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - The Philanderer, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - The Piano Lesson, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - The Possessed, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - The Revenger's Tragedy, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - The Road to Mecca, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - The Seagull, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - The Solid Gold Cadillac, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - The Suicide, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - The Vietnamization of New Jersey, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - The Wild Duck, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - They are Dying Out, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - Timon of Athens, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Twelfth Night, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - Two Trains Running, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Uncle Vanya, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Underground, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Victory, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - We Bombed in New Haven, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - What the Butler Saw, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Where Has Tommy Flowers Gone?, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - White Marriage, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Wings, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Winterfest
    - 2, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
    - 3, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
    - 4, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - 5, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
    - 6, 1985-1986 (Box 2)
    - 7, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
    - 8, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
    - 9, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
    - 10, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
    - 11, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Woyzeck and Play, 1970-1971 (Box 2)